# Hany Magdy Front-end Developer

- Many.magdy25@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/hanymagdy-7a0ab4175
- Mansoura, Egypt

# +20 1112994482

- https://github.com/HanyMagdy25
- Exempted from military service

## **₽** Profile

Passionate Front-End Developer having around two years extensive experience in Front-end development ,I am seeking for a challenging and prospective opportunity as Frontend developer in a company with a good reputation that

will add to my knowledge, skills and experience.

# **Education**

# Mansoura University

Bachelor degree In Computer Science Sep 2017 – Jun 2021 | Mansoura, Egypt

# Projects

#### Edrak 🛮

I have created a big articles website with many features and a dashboard using React JS and redux , finally connected it with the API

# Opia-Levant 🛮

I have created a menu and table reservations with react js with many features and pagination

## 

I have created Shorouk Specialised Hospital website with many features using React.js

## Food Market 🛮

I have created food market website with many features like adding any product to favourite page or cart page and calculate your receipt using React.js and Context API

#### Textgenuss 🛮

I have created a big courses website with many features and a dashboard using React JS , finally connected it with the API

#### Movix 🛮

I have created a movies website using Reactjs and Redux-Toolkit with great features like adding a movie to the watch list and remove it from there if you want

# Portfolio for a client with React JS 🛮

I have created a portfolio for a client with react js with many features like sending messages to his email and to display his works.

# **Experience**

#### Technomasr for web solutions ☑

Front-end Developer Dec 2022 – present | Egypt

### **Software Cloud 2**

Front-End Developer
Aug 2022 – Nov 2022
Integrating and implementing new
features using React js technologies.

#### Depax

Front-end Developer
Mar 2022 – Jul 2022
Mansoura, Egypt
Work hand in hand with backend
developers and designers to meet
product expectations and deadlines.
Integrating and implementing new
features using React js technologies.

## Freelance

Front End Developer
Jul 2021 – Dec 2021 | Mansoura, Egypt

# ဦး Skills

HTML5 | CSS3 | Tailwind

JavaScript | TypeScript | React JS

Next.js | Redux | SCSS

Bootstrap | Material UI